{
  "2025-04-25": {
    "title": "The Premier Club",
    "clues": [
      {
        "id": 0,
        "question": "An american propaganda character's store similar to Costco.",
        "answer": "Uncle Sam's Club",
        "solved": false
      },
      {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "A popular hip hop artist moves into a section of the White House",
        "answer": "Kanye West Wing",
        "solved": false
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "Pixar character Joy moves to Alaska to hit the slopes with Zach Galifianakis in this crossover film",
        "answer": "Inside Out Cold",
        "solved": false
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "An american rock band since '91 named after their front-man covers a song by Paul Mccartney & The Wings featuring an unexpected verse from a hip-hop superduo.",
        "answer": "Dave Matthews Band on the Run the Jewels",
        "solved": false
      }
    ],
    "extraWords": [
      "bang", "2", "snoop", "kendrick", "nas", "lil", "cube", "frost", 
      "icicle", "freeze", "frigid", "chill", "bar", "pub", "lounge", "annex", 
      "balcony", "aunt", "cousin", "music", "black", "dash", "jog", 
      "sprint", "gems", "ruby", "within", "outside", "upon", "arm"
    ]
  },
  "2025-04-26": {
    "title": "Grab Bag of Holding",
    "clues": [
      {
        "id": 0,
        "question": "Rihanna's EDM hit searches for singles in paradise on reality TV.",
        "answer": "We Found Love Island",
        "solved": false
      },
      {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "Mouselike boy in an E.B. White story traveling through the heavens as Ursa Minor.",
        "answer": "Stuart Little Dipper",
        "solved": false
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "The famed Bourbon street area of New Orleans serves a classic fast food burger.",
        "answer": "French Quarter Pounder",
        "solved": false
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "A dyed object hunted for on resurrection Sunday, with fried Chinese appetizers becomes an Alabama football rally cry.",
        "answer": "Easter Egg Roll Tide",
        "solved": false
      }
    ],
    "extraWords": [
      "work", "diamonds", "hot", "24", "whopper", "bacon", "double", "elf", "Chris", "baker", "a",
      "rah", "jesus", "crab", "stars", "Jacob", "fun", "yeah"
    ]
  },
  "2025-04-27": {
    "title": "Grab Bag of Tricks",
    "clues": [
      {
        "id": 0,
        "question": "A 1946 film following George Bailey's Christmas Eve takes a turn when he grabs this item to survive a sinking ship.",
        "answer": "A Beautiful Life Jacket",
        "solved": false
      },
      {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "Ice cream parlor favorite faces an uncertain call from boxing judges.",
        "answer": "Banana Split Decision",
        "solved": false
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "A viral simple game with one button becomes an item for some feathered flyers to take a drink or cool off.",
        "answer": "Flappy Bird Bath",
        "solved": false
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "A non-verbal response to someone saying something stupid ends up hurting so bad you get pain in your cranium and then in your chest.",
        "answer": "Shaking My Head Ache-y Breaky Heart",
        "solved": false
      } 
    ],
    "extraWords": [
      "citizen", "santa", "the", "cone", "chocolate", "vanilla", "minecraft", "pong", "blood", "water", "shower",
      "eagle", "whipped", "cream", "any", "from", "but", "torso"
    ]
  },
  "2025-04-28": {
    "title": "The Windy City Lights",
    "clues": [
      {
        "id": 0,
        "question": "An Adele single about a Chicago staple.",
        "answer": "Rolling in the Deep Dish",
        "solved": false
      },
      {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "A Snoop Dogg single about a Chicago-styled food.",
        "answer": "Drop It Like It's Hot Dog",
        "solved": false
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "A windy city team goes marching to a Rage against the Machine song.",
        "answer": "Chicago Bulls on Parade",
        "solved": false
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "An '80s classic filmed in Chicago features a car riding through dirt listening to a single by the Talking Heads.",
        "answer": "Ferris Bueller's Day Off Road to Nowhere",
        "solved": false
      } 
    ],
    "extraWords": [
      "chicago", "sears", "sausage", "cubs", "bears", "madison", "new", "york", "single", "3", "more", "better",
      "shake", "weed", "smoke", "blues", "brothers"
    ]
  },
  "2025-04-29": {
    "title": "Granny Shot in the Dark",
    "clues": [
      {
        "id": 0,
        "question": "An Arrested Development child becomes a hoops legend.",
        "answer": "George Michael Jordan",
        "solved": false
      },
      {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "A Boston Celtics superstar succumbs to the H5N1 virus.",
        "answer": "Larry Bird Flu",
        "solved": false
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "A potential 3 point basketball play sung about by Harry Styles and others.",
        "answer": "And One Direction",
        "solved": false
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "Nicole Kidman and Sandra Bullock use their witchcraft to play ball with a famed HIV-postive basketball player who works for a pharmaceutical industry company.",
        "answer": "Practical Magic Johnson & Johnson",
        "solved": false
      }
    ],
    "extraWords": [
      "aids", "jr", "sr", "bluth", "blue", "russell", "steph", "curry", "kobe", "dark", "black", "abbott", "three", "play", "bounce", "with", "a", "the", "boys"
    ]
  },
  "2025-05-01": {
    "title": "Marvel at the Sight Unseen",
    "clues": [
      {
        "id": 0,
        "question": "The first MCU film gets played for a club who won the premier league from 2020-2023 (nickname).",
        "answer": "Iron Man City",
        "solved": false
      },
      {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "Imposter Ned Schneebly plays a role alongside the MCU's T'Challa.",
        "answer": "Jack Black Panther",
        "solved": false
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "A famous phrase reminding us that making mistakes is part of being mortal is spoken by a fiery Fantastic Four member who may have been denied a bank loan.",
        "answer": "To Err is Human Torch",
        "solved": false
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "Groot and friends have increasingly genius ideas like a space-y meme. Unfortunately, they're so good it makes their head hurt like they just chugged a slushie.", 
        "answer": "Guardians of the Galaxy Brain Freeze",
        "solved": false
      }
    ],
    "extraWords": [
      "cream", "a", "we", "&", "boys", "space", "joker", "club", "football", "captain", "america", "wanda", "blue", "up", "faking", "company", "friends", "bad", "oops"
    ]
  },
  "2025-05-02": {
    "title": "Video Game of Life",
    "clues": [
      {
        "id": 0,
        "question": "Nintendo friends play games with a bunch of LA waiters on a 2009 American sitcom.",
        "answer": "Mario Party Down",
        "solved": false
      },
      {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "A Bruce Springsteen song featuring the refrain 'You can't start a fire without a spark' is played over a popular FromSoftware video game series.",
        "answer": "Dancing in the Dark Souls",
        "solved": false
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "Mike Myers and Dana Carvey explore Azeroth as orcs.",
        "answer": "Wayne's World of Warcraft",
        "solved": false
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "A slang for 'being real' or 'being honest' and eating a candy bar with chocolate, caramel, and crisped rice while stealing cars and shooting people up in an open world video game.", 
        "answer": "Keeping it 100 Grand Theft Auto",
        "solved": false
      }
    ],
    "extraWords": [
      "bad", "james", "bond", "zelda", "austin", "playstation", "street", "fight", "a", "us", "bar", "3", "dew", "trust", "atari", "mission", "yoshi", "phone" 
    ]
  },
  "2025-05-03": {
    "title": "Lebron James Bond",
    "clues": [
      {
        "id": 0,
        "question": "The first film in the James Bond series features a song by TLC. (It's still not a medical film).",
        "answer": "Dr. No Scrubs",
        "solved": false
      },
      {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "The second film in the James Bond series is filmed on a land mass in Fiji where sexy singles couple up in a reality show. (it was notably NOT filmed in the country in it's name).",
        "answer": "From Russia with Love Island",
        "solved": false
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "A Pierce Brosnan Bond flick is watched during an early November Mexican holiday. (Not the film that actually has a scene at a parade for that holiday).",
        "answer": "Die Another Day of the Dead",
        "solved": false
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "The most recent Bond portrayer runs the warehouse of a paper company and doubles as a gay CNN broadcast journalist/political commentator.", 
        "answer": "Daniel Craig Anderson Cooper",
        "solved": false
      }
    ],
    "extraWords": [
      "golden", "eye", "sean", "thomas", "spy", "diamonds", "only", "sky", "casino", "hank", "italy", "korea", "china", "man", "gun"
    ]
  },
  "2025-05-05": {
    "title": "Fast Food Fight",
    "clues": [
      {
        "id": 0,
        "question": "A classic American fast food chain is visited by a British folk hero who wields a mythical sword.",
        "answer": "Burger King Arthur",
        "solved": false
      },
      {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "An 'Yum!' fast food chain features a vegetable that primarily comes in green, red, yellow or orange.",
        "answer": "Taco Bell Pepper",
        "solved": false
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "A dessert-forward fast food chain is visited by a rapper/singer/actress born Dana Elaine Owens.",
        "answer": "Dairy Queen Latifah",
        "solved": false
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "The restaurant famed for its secret blend of 11 herbs and spices inspires a hen to warn that the sky is falling, raining down hot n ready pizzas.",
        "answer": "Kentucky Fried Chicken Little Caesars",
        "solved": false
      }
    ],
    "extraWords": [
      "big", "mac", "crunchwrap", "silvers", "panda", "mcdonalds", "quarter", "cheese", "sauce", "big", "dennys", "dinner", "snack", "with", "a", "the", "boys", "free"
    ]
  }
} 